Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Charles H. W. Foster, 1965-1980; Accession 1983-A-019
  - Record, Samuel J.-Wood Collection, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - San Francisco, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - School Outdoor Weekend, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - School Policy, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Semester at Yale Program, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - "Social, Economic, Ethical, and Legal Aspects of Natural Resource Management" Fund Raising Committee for Proposal, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Society of American Foresters-New England Section, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Special Projects-Revolving Scholarship Fund, undated (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Special Students, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Students, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Wildlife Programs, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Yale-Appointment, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Yale-Current, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Yale Faculty Research Fellowships, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 91-92)
  - Miscellaneous printed material, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 93-103, Box 9)
- Records of Charles H. W. Foster, 1959-1983; Accession 1983-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018
  - Administrative Files Within the Forestry School, Series I
    Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
    - Alumni Fund, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - Industrial Forestry Seminars, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Faccom [Faculty Committees]
      - Faculty searches and directives, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Seminar Series, 1964-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Seminar Series, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8-12)
      - Wildlife professor, search for, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Revolving Scholarship Fund, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
    - Yankee Forest, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16-19)
  - Administrative Files Outside Yale
    - F, 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United States, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Forest Products Research Society, 1961-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Fulbright Scholarships, 1966-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - G, 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Study in Biology, guide to, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - H (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
    - Hardwood Research Center (proposed), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Harvard Forest, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
    - Harvard-Yale, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
    - Housatonic Valley Association, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Human Environment Center, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - I, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Institute for Community Economics, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Institute of Ecology, 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Institute on Man and Science, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - International Salmon Foundation, 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 21-23)
    - International Union for Conservation of Nature, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - International Union of Forestry Research Organizations, 1971-1980 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - J, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Jaakko Pöyry (consulting organization), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - K, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - L, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 29-30)
    - Library of Commerce, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - M, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 32-33)
    - Marine Fisheries Advisory Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 34-36)
    - Marine Fisheries Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 37-38)
    - Massachusetts Board of Natural Resources, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Massachusetts Department of Environmental Management, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - N, 1971-1980 (Box 8, Folder 41-43)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1972-1980 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - National Park Service, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 45-49)
    - National Planning Association, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - National Science Foundation, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 51-53)
    - Nature Conservancy, 1973-1980 (Box 10, Folder 54-55)
    - New Hampshire Forests: Society of Protection, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Resource Planning Associates, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Resource Policy Center, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Resources for the Future, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Rhode Island Audubon Society, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - S, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 61-62)
    - Salmon, Atlantic, Restoration of, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Society of American Foresters
      - Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 11, Folder 64-66)
      - Meetings, 1971-1978 (Box 12, Folder 67-69)
      - New England section, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Reorganization, Federal, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 71-75)
      - Student Chapters, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Soil Conservation Service, 1976-1980 (Box 14, Folder 77-78)
    - Student Conservation Association, 1974-1979 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Sturbridge Village Project, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - T, 1976-1980 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Trust for Public Land, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 82-83)
    - Trustees for Reservations, Massachusetts, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 83A)
    - U, 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - United States Department of Agriculture: Forest Service, 1971-1980 (Box 15, Folder 85-87)
    - United States Department of Agriculture: Forest Service, 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 88-89)
    - United States Department of Commerce: Natural Marine Fisheries, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - United States Department of Energy, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - United States Department of the Interior, 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 92-93)
    - University of Connecticut, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - V-W, 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 95-97)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute
      - 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 99-101)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 102)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 103-106)
      - Corporation and Trustees meetings
        - 1976-1977 (Box 18)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 107-111)
    - "Woodworks", a design for an exhibit to be installed in a new Department of Environmental Management Visitor Center, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Campaign for Yale, Series III
    Restricted to office of origin only.
    - A, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Always a Pioneer: brochure, School of Forestry, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
    - Awards: Forestry, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - B, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Brochures sent, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - C, 1959-1968 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Career Seminar, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Companies: fund raising, 1963-1966 (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Comment, letters of, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Comments from faculty, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Contributions to Forestry School Program, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, early. K. Brewster and J. Miller: setting up Committees, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Committees, meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Development, Office of, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - E-F, 1961-1965 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - East Texas Pulp and Paper (Time, Inc.), 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Faculty suggestions and plans, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Finnish proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Fleischmann Foundation, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Fund raising meeting, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Fund raising plan revised, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Georgia-Pacific, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Glatfelter Company, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - H, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Health, Education and Welfare: Mini grant, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Hammermill Paper Company, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Hines, Edward Lumber Company, 1967-1975 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Huber, J.M. Corporation, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - I-J, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Independent School Consultants, undated (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Iranian proposal, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Kimberly-Clark Corporation, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - M, 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Memoranda, correspondence: (miscellaneous fund raising material), 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - N, 1956-1967 (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - News Releases, pamphlets, 1967-1975 (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Oceanograph/Limnology project, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Olinkraft Incorporated, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Outdoor Weekend (Yale Outdoor Recreation), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - P-Q, 1966-1970 (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Procter and Gamble, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Progress Report, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - Proposal for Fund Raising Program: tentative, 1965-1971 (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Prospects (fund raising), 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Prospect list, 1966-1974 (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Publications, 1963-1974 (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - R, 1960-1971 (Box 24, Folder 79)
    - Riegel Paper Corporation, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 80)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 81)
    - Rowe, Stanley M., Sr.: Cincinnati Nature Center, 1966-1974 (Box 24, Folder 83)
    - S, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 84)
    - Scott Paper Company, 1967-1971 (Box 24, Folder 85)
    - Simpson Timber Company, 1976-1970 (Box 24, Folder 86)
    - T, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 88)
    - Telephone receipts, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 89)
    - Templeton Foundation, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 90)
    - United States Department of Agriculture Forest Service, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 94)
    - United States Information Agency, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 95)
    - Washington Technical Institute: minorities, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 99)
    - XYZ, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 103)
- Records of George A. Garratt, 1941-1970; Accession 1984-A-014
  - Yale, 1950-1970
    - Alumni Fund
      - Correspondence
        - 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
        - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
        - 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
        - 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Lists
        - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Appointment Calendars
      - 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Boston Meeting, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Brochure, Forestry School, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Communism at Yale, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Foundations, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Fundraising correspondence and lists
      - 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
      - 1952-1958 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - 1952-1961 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - 1953-1958 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - 1954 (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
      - 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - 1956-1964 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - 1957-1966 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Canadian Companies, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Cascade Lumber Co., 1952-1957 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Champion Paper and Fibre Co., 1954-1960 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Crossett Company, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Crown Zellerbach Corp., 1952-1957 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Dead River Company, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Flintkote Company, 1954-1957 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Gaylord Container Co., 1952-1956 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - General Box Company, 1952-1956 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Graves Memorial Fund, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - Graves Memorial Fund, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Great Northern Paper Co., 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Hines Lumber Co., 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Hollingsworth and Whitney, Co., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - International Paper Company, 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Ketchikan Pulp Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Mengel Co., 1953-1955 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Michigan-California Lumber Co., 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Oxford Paper Co., 1953-1957 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Penobscot Chemical Fibre Co., 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - St. Croix Paper Co., 1953-1957 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - St. Paul and Tacoma Lumber Co., 1952-1957 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Sinpson Timber Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Tacoma and Seattle, 1952-1958 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Trip to Midwest, 1954-1958 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Wardwell, Ranney, and Allen, 1953-1960 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Co., 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Wood Conservation Foundation, 1953-1957 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Propaganda General, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Industrial Forestry Program at YSF, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Long Range Development, Committee on
      - 1963 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - 1964 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Long-Range Goals, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Long-Range Planning, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Personal-Correspondence and Biographical Notes, 1944-1970 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Publicity-Yale School of Forestry, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Reports-Yale School of Forestry, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Report-"The Treatability of Angelique", 1953 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - School of Forestry Memoranda, 1922-1976 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Speeches-Des Moines Convention, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - University Council
      - 1961 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 91)
      - 1962 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      - 1963 (Box 7, Folder 93-95)
      - 1964 (Box 7, Folder 96)
      - 1965 (Box 7, Folder 97)
      - Preliminary Report, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - Reports on Forestry School, 1951-1966 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Connecticut Organizations
    - Algonquin State Forest, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Capitol Regions Planning Agency
      - 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Committee for Outdoor Recreation Resources, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Clean Water Task Force, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Conn. River National Recreation Area Study, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Council on Agriculture, Conservation and Natural Resources
      - 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
      - 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Natural Resources
      - Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, Legislation
        - 1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
        - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
        - 1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
        - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 13)
        - 1967 (Box 9, Folder 14)
        - 1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        - 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Management Reports
        - Manual of Procedures, 1960 June (Box 9, Folder 17)
        - Surveys, 1960 November (Box 9, Folder 18)
        - Bureau of Business Administration, 1960 April (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Publications, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Auditors" Report, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Forest and Park Association, 1962-1966 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Great Mountain Forest Corporation
    - History of Forestry in Connecticut, 1901-1954 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Interregional Planning Program
      - Newsletters, Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Printed Material, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
    - Nassahegon State Forest, Working Plan, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Natural Resources Council of Conn.
      - 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Open Space Program, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rocky Neck State Park Pipeline Easement, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Shenipsit Forest, Proposed Recreation Areas, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - State Development Commission, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - State Forest Recreational Facilities, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - State Park and Forest Commission
      - Correspondence, Memoranda, etc.
        - 1943-1947 (Box 11, Folder 35)
        - 1949-1962 (Box 11, Folder 36)
        - 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 37)
        - 1960-1964 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Chapman: correspondence re. Personnel conflict, 1942-1945 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Camping Report, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Field Trip Baedecker, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Forest Commission
        - 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 42)
        - 1963 (Box 12, Folder 43)
        - 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 44)
        - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 45-49)
        - 1965 (Box 12, Folder 50-51)
        - 1965 (Box 13, Folder 52-55)
        - 1966 (Box 13, Folder 56-57)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 58-59)
        - 1967 (Box 13, Folder 60)
        - 1959-1967 (Box 13, Folder 61)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 62-63)
        - 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 64)
        - 1968 (Box 14, Folder 65)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 66)
        - 1969 (Box 14, Folder 67-69)
      - Park Committee Boating Report (Box 14, Folder 70)
      - Minutes
        - 1959 Jan-Dec (Box 15, Folder 71)
        - 1960 Jan-Dec (Box 15, Folder 72)
        - 1961 Jan-Dec (Box 15, Folder 73)
        - 1962 Jan-Dec (Box 15, Folder 74)
        - 1963 Jan-Dec (Box 15, Folder 75)
        - 1964 Jan-1965 Jun (Box 15, Folder 76)
      - Publications
        - 1921-1944 (Box 15, Folder 77)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 78)
      - General Survey, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 79)
      - Receipts, Expenditures, Attendance, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 80)
      - Auditors" Report, 1954-1956, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 81)
      - Misc: Correspondence, Clippings, Legislation, 1950-1962 (Box 16, Folder 82-84)
      - Misc. Pamphlets and Publications, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Outside Connecticut Organizations
    - Forestry Studies
      - Forestry in the USSR
        - Reports, Pamphlets, Maps, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
        - Publications, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Forestry Education Study in Canada
        - Questionnaires-English, prior to 1961 (Box 17, Folder 4-7)
        - Questionnaires-English, prior to 1961 (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
        - Questionnaires-French, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 10-13)
        - Questionnaire Data, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
        - Request for unreturned questionnaires, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
        - Forestry in Canada, 1946-1967 (Box 19, Folder 16)
        - British Columbia Forest Service, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - Newfoundland Forest Service, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 18)
        - Forest Ranger School Survey, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
        - Canadian Council of Resource Ministers Draft of Report: Natural Resource Management Education, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 20)
        - Canadian Institute of Forestry Data re: Forestry Education Study, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 21)
        - Dept. of Forestry, Annual Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 22)
        - Printed material, 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 23)
        - British Columbia, University of
          - Correspondence and memoranda, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 24)
          - Questionnaires, undated (Box 19, Folder 25-26)
          - Questionnaire and related items, 1958-1967 (Box 20, Folder 27)
          - Questionnaire Study, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 28)
          - Paper: "A First Look at Watershed Management Problems and Research Needs in British Columbia"Â, 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 29)
          - Academic Program, Report of Committee, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 30)
          - Projected Curriculum 1967-1968, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 31)
          - Bulletins, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 32)
          - Establishment of Forestry Dept., undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
          - Annual Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 20, Folder 34)
          - Booklets, 1945-1966 (Box 20, Folder 35)
        - New Brunswick, University of
          - Questionnaire Data, 1963-1968 (Box 20, Folder 36)
          - Questionnaire Study, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 37)
          - Calendar 1965-1966, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 38)
          - Forest Engineering degree course info., 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 39)
          - Faculty of Forestry Brochures, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 40)
          - Draft of pamphlet about University, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 41)
        - Toronto, University of
          - Questionnaire Study, correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 42)
          - Questionnaire replies, graduate list, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 43)
          - Establishment of the University (Box 21, Folder 44)
        - Society of Wood Science and Technology Education Study, 1960-1965 (Box 21, Folder 45)
        - Study of Forest Technician Training
          - Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 46)
          - University Forestry Programs, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 47-48)
        - Duke Accreditation Study, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Courses during WWII
      - Correspondence and descriptions, 1941-1945 (Box 22, Folder 50-51)
      - Outlines, 1942-1945 (Box 22, Folder 52-53)
      - Outlines, 1942-1945 (Box 23, Folder 54-55)
      - Outlines for container courses, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 56-57)
    - Organizations
      - Ford Foundation Project, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 58)
      - Forest History Society
        - Correspondence
          - 1963 (Box 23, Folder 59)
          - 1964 (Box 23, Folder 60)
          - 1965 (Box 23, Folder 61)
          - 1966 (Box 23, Folder 62)
          - 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 63)
        - Reports, Correspondence, minutes, bylaws, etc., 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 64-65)
        - Minutes
          - 1965 Jun 4 (Box 24, Folder 66)
          - 1966 May 19 (Box 24, Folder 67)
          - 1966 Oct 14 (Box 24, Folder 68)
          - 1967 Feb 3 (Box 24, Folder 69)
          - 1967 Oct 24 (Box 24, Folder 70)
          - 1968 Feb 22 (Box 24, Folder 71)
          - 1968 Apr 23 (Box 24, Folder 72)
          - 1969 Jun 4 (Box 24, Folder 73)
      - Forest Products Research Society-correspondence, minutes, reports, etc., 1962-1970 (Box 24, Folder 74)
      - Forest Research Advisory Committee-correspondence, pamphlets, 1960-1964 (Box 25, Folder 75)
      - Foundation for Professional Forestry-correspondence, Reports, Finances, 1963-1968 (Box 25, Folder 76)
      - Journal of Forestry-editing of articles
        - 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 77)
        - 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 78)
      - Northeastern Forest Research Advisory Council-correspondence, reports, minutes
        - 1958-1962 (Box 25, Folder 79)
        - 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 80)
        - 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 81)
      - Professional Manpower, Advisory Committee on, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 82)
      - Public Land Law Review Commission, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 83)
      - Science Advisory Committee-correspondence, memoranda, reports, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 84)
      - Society of American Foresters
      - Correspondence
        - 1958 (Box 26, Folder 85)
        - 1959 (Box 26, Folder 86-88)
        - 1960 (Box 27, Folder 89-91)
        - 1961 (Box 27, Folder 92-94)
        - 1962 (Box 27, Folder 95-96)
        - 1963 (Box 28, Folder 97)
        - 1964 (Box 28, Folder 98)
        - 1965-1970 (Box 28, Folder 99)
      - Forestry Education Study (Box 28, Folder 100)
      - Reports, Newsletters, Papers, 1946-1960 (Box 28, Folder 101)
      - Visiting Scientists Program
        - 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 102)
        - 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 103)
      - Policy Statements (Box 28, Folder 104)
      - Endowment Fund, 1962-1968 (Box 28, Folder 105-107)
      - Society of Wood Science and Technology
        - Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 108)
        - Newsletters
          - 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 109)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 110)